//Add Questions (Array of Objects)
const quiz = [
    {
        question:"When the Turkish President and founder of the Republic of Turkey, Mustafa Kemal Atat√ºrk, transformed the Hagia Sophia building into a Museum?",
        options:["1940", "1935", "1949", "1901"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"The Second largest Gas field of Pakistan is__________?",
        options:["Qadirpur Gas Field", "Uch Gas Field", " Bobi Gas Field", "Chachar Gas Field"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"How many countries are there in Asia?",
        options:["50", "46", "49", "48"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"Pakistan number in the world population-wise on _________ number?",
        options:["6th", "10th", "5th", "11th"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"How many currencies are in the world?",
        options:["180", "90", "195", "190"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following countries has the largest area in the world ?",
        options:["USA", "Russia", "China", "India"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"The major source of water in Pakistan is___________?",
        options:["Rain", "Lakes", "Rivers", "Snow"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"In which country paper was first invented?",
        options:["Germany", "Finland", "Netherland", "China"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"Nelson Mandela got Nishan e Pakistan in which year?",
        options:["1990", "1992", "1991", "1993"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"Who is the most elected Prime Minister in Pakistan?",
        options:["Imran Khan", "Benazir Bhutto", "Nawaz Shareef", "Yousuf Raza Gillani"],
        answer:2
    }
]